name: Minecraft Crafting Recipes
authors:
  - mfnalex
questions:
  - question: "A spyglass can be crafted with two copper ingots and one ..."
    answers:
      - "Amethyst Shard"
  - question: "A hay bale consists of how many wheat?"
    answers:
      - 9
      - nine
  - question: "A full set of armor requires how many pieces of the same material?"
    answers:
      - 24
      - twentyfour
      - twenty four
      - twenty-four
  - question: "How many different wood types exist (without those of nether trees)?"
    answers:
      - 7
      - seven
  - question: "What's the main ingredient for scaffolding?"
    answers:
      - "Bamboo"
  - question: "TNT can be crafted with gunpowder and ..."
    answers:
      - "Sand"
  - question: "What's the only craftable music disc?"
    answers:
      - "Music Disc 5"
      - 5
      - "Five"
      - Music Disc Five
      - Music Disc (5)
      - Music Disc (Five)
  - question: "A Compass and 8 Echo Shards can be crafted into ..."
    answers:
      - "Recovery Compass"
  - question: "What kind of ingots are required to craft a blast furnace?"
    answers:
      - "Iron ingot"
      - "Iron"
  - question: "A target block consists of 4 redstone and 1 ..."
    answers:
      - "Hay bale"
      - "hay block"
      - "Hay"
  - question: "Coarse Dirt can be crafted with 2 dirt and 2 ..."
    answers:
      - "Gravel"
  - question: "A Respawn Anchor consists of glowstone and ..."
    answers:
      - "Crying Obsidian"
  - question: "A Glistering Melon Slice consists of a Melon Slice and eight ..."
    answers:
      - "Gold Nuggets"
      - "Gold Nugget"
  - question: "A Brewing Stand requires a blaze rod and ..."
    answers:
      - "Cobblestone"
      - "Cobble stone"
  - question: "A Lightning Rod can be crafted with ..."
    answers:
      - "Copper ingots"
      - "Copper ingot"
  - question: "The difference between a Dropper's and a Dispenser's crafting recipe is what item?"
    answers:
      - "Bow"
  - question: "A Fire Charge requires coal, gunpowder, and ..."
    answers:
      - "Blaze Powder"
  - question: "Magma Blocks can be crafted with four ..."
    answers:
      - "Magma Cream"
  - question: "Diorite and Nether Quartz can be crafted into what?"
    answers:
      - "Granite"
  - question: "A Book and Quill can be crafted using a book, a feather and ..."
    answers:
      - "Ink Sac"
      - "Ink Sack"
      - "inksac"
      - "inksack"
  - question: "A Beacon consists of 5 glass, 3 obsidian and 1 ..."
    answers:
      - "Nether Star"
  - question: "The only thing you can craft with exactly 3 Bricks (NOT Brick Blocks) is what?"
    answers:
      - "Flower Pot"
  - question: "A Lead consists of four string and one ..."
    answers:
      - "Slimeball"
      - "Slime ball"
  - question: "A grindstone consists of two planks, one stone slab, and two ..."
    answers:
      - "Sticks"
      - "stick"
  - question: "7 Glass, 1 Eye of Ender and 1 Ghast Tear result in what?"
    answers:
      - "End Crystal"
  - question: "Cooked Rabbit + Carrot + Mushroom + Bowl + ... = Rabbit Stew"
    answers:
      - "Baked Potato"
      - "Baked Potatoes"
      - "Cooked Potato"
      - "Cooked Potatoes"
  - question: "The difference between a ... and a Suspicious Stew is a flower."
    answers:
      - "Mushroom Stew"
      - "Mushroom soup"
  - question: "What flower is required to craft a Suspicious Stew of Night Vision?"
    answers:
      - "Poppy"
  - question: "What flower is required to craft a Suspicious Stew of Poison?"
    answers:
      - "Lily of the Valley"
  - question: "What flower is required to craft a Suspicious Stew of Weakness?"
    answers:
      - "Tulips"
      - "Tulip"
  - question: "A Suspicious Stew with a Cornflower gives what potion effect?"
    answers:
      - "Jump Boost"
  - question: "A Suspicous Stew with a Blue Orchid gives what potion effect?"
    answers:
      - "Saturation"
  - question: "A Suspicious Stew with an Oxeye Daisy gives what potion effect?"
    answers:
      - "Regeneration"
  - question: "Black Dye can be crafted with an Ink Sac, or ..."
    answers:
      - "Wither Rose"
  - question: "Which potion ingredient is required for the Weakness effect?"
    answers:
      - "Fermented Spider Eye"
  - question: "An Awkward Potion is brewed using ..."
    answers:
      - "Nether Warts"
      - "Nether wart"
      - "Netherwarts"
      - "Netherwart"
  - question: "Splash Potions are brewed using ..."
    answers:
      - "Gunpowder"
      - "gun powder"
  - question: "A Splash Potion can be turned into a Lingering Potion using ..."
    answers:
      - "Dragon's Breath"
      - "Dragons breath"
      - "Dragon breath"
  - question: "A Potion of Swiftness is brewed by adding what to an Awkward Potion?"
    answers:
      - "Sugar"
  - question: "A Potion of of Leaping is brewed by adding what to an Awkward Potion?"
    answers:
      - "Rabbit's Foot"
      - "Rabbits foot"
      - "Rabbit foot"
  - question: "A Potion of Healing is brewed by adding what to an Awkward Potion?"
    answers:
      - "Glistering Melon Slice"
      - "Glistering Melon"
  - question: "A Potion of Strength is brewed by adding what to an Awkward Potion?"
    answers:
      - "Blaze Powder"
  - question: "A Potion of Poison is brewed by adding what to an Awkward Potion?"
    answers:
      - "Spider Eye"
  - question: "A Potion of Regeneration is brewed by adding what to an Awkward Potion?"
    answers:
      - "Ghast Tear"
  - question: "A Potion of Fire Resistance is brewed by adding what to an Awkward Potion?"
    answers:
      - "Magma Cream"
  - question: "A Potion of Water Breathing is brewed by adding what to an Awkward Potion?"
    answers:
      - "Pufferfish"
      - "Puffer fish"
  - question: "A Potion of Night Vision is brewed by adding what to an Awkward Potion?"
    answers:
      - "Golden Carrot"
  - question: "A Potion of Night Vision can be turned into a Potion of Invisibility by adding what?"
    answers:
      - "Fermented Spider Eye"
  - question: "A Potion of the Turtle Master is brewed by adding what to an Awkward Potion?"
    answers:
      - "Turtle Shell"
  - question: "A Potion of Slow Falling is brewed by adding what to an Awkward Potion?"
    answers:
      - "Phantom Membrane"
  - question: "Elytras can be repaired on an anvil using what?"
    answers:
      - "Phantom Membranes"
      - "Phantom Membrane"
  - question: "You lost your last End Rod and want to craft a new one. What do you need, besides a blaze rod?"
    answers:
      - "Popped Chorus Fruit"
  - question: "Four Popped Chorus Fruit can be crafted into what?"
    answers:
      - "Purpur Block"
  - question: "A barrel can be crafted using 6 wooden planks and 2 ..."
    answers:
      - "Wooden Slabs"
      - "Wood slabs"
  - question: "A smoker consists of a furnace and four ... ?"
    answers:
      - "Logs"
  - question: "What's needed for a Fletching Table besides wooden planks?"
    answers:
      - "Flints"
      - "Flint"
  - question: "An ingot of Netherite requires gold ingots and ..."
    answers:
      - "Netherite Scraps"
      - "Netherite Scrap"
  - question: "A Lodestone can be crafted using 1 Netherite Ingot and 8 ..."
    answers:
      - "Chiseled Stone Bricks"
      - "Chiseled Stonebricks"
      - "Chiseled Stone Brick"
      - "Chiseled Stonebrick"
  - question: "Honeycomb + ... = Candle"
    answers:
      - "String"
      - "Strings"
  - question: "What do you need to turn Glass into Tinted Glass?"
    answers:
      - "Amethyst Shards"
      - "Amethyst Shard"
  - question: "Combining a Slimeball and Blaze Powder results in what?"
    answers:
      - "Magma Cream"
  - question: "An Activator Rail requires Iron Ingots, Sticks, and what?"
    answers:
      - "Redstone Torch"
      - "Redstone Torches"
  - question: "A Daylight Detector can be crafted using 3 Glass, 3 Wooden Slabs, and 3 ..."
    answers:
      - "Nether Quartz"
  - question: "Red Nether Bricks require an equal amount of Nether Bricks and ..."
    answers:
      - "Nether Warts"
      - "Nether wart"
  - question: "A Sea Lantern consists of 4 Prismarine Shards and 5 ..."
    answers:
      - "Prismarine Crystals"
      - "Prismarine Crystal"
  - question: "Cobblestone and Diorite can be combined into ..."
    answers:
      - "Andesite"
  - question: "A Purpur Pillar consists of two ..."
    answers:
      - "Purpur Slabs"
      - "Purpur Slab"
  - question: "A Conduit can be crafted using 8 Nautilus Shells and 1 ..."
    answers:
      - "Heart of the Sea"
      - "Heart of the Seas"
  - question: "A Conduit can be crafted using 1 Heart of the Sea and 8 ..."
    answers:
      - "Nautilus Shells"
      - "Nautilus Shell"
  - question: "1 Iron Ingot + 2 ... = 1 Chain"
    answers:
      - "Iron Nuggets"
      - "Iron Nugget"
  - question: "How many blocks of the same type are required to craft 8 stairs?"
    answers:
      - "12"
      - "twelve"
  - question: "How many pieces of paper do you need for a level 30 Enchanting Table (including the Bookshelves and the Enchanting Table itself)?"
    answers:
      - "138"
  - question: "How many pieces of leather do you need for a level 30 Enchanting Table (including the Bookshelves and the Enchanting Table itself)"
    answers:
      - "46"
      - "fourty six"
      - "fourtysix"
      - "fourty-six"
  - question: "A Dripstone Block consists of four ..."
    answers:
    - "Pointed Dripstones"
    - "Pointed dripstone"
  - question: "Diorite can be crafted using Nether Quartz and what?"
    answers:
      - "Cobblestone"
      - "Cobble stone"
  - question: "Tripwire Hook + Chest = ..."
    answers:
      - "Trapped Chest"
  - question: "6 Sticks + 1 ... = Armor Stand"
    answers:
      - "Smooth Stone Slab"
  - question: "1 Soul Torch + 8 ... = Soul Lantern"
    answers:
      - "Iron Nuggets"
      - "Iron nugget"
  - question: "A Soul Torch is crafted using a coal, a stick, and ..."
    answers:
      - "Soul Soil or Soul Sand"
      - "Soul Soil"
      - "Soul Sand"
  - question: "How many stacks of Sticks can you craft out of one stack of Logs?"
    answers:
      - "8"
      - "eight"
  - question: "How many ladders can you craft out of 10 Logs?"
    answers:
      - "33"
      - "thirty three"
      - "thirty-three"
      - "thirtythree"
  - question: "How many Glass Panes can you craft out of one stack of Glass?"
    answers:
      - "160"
  - question: "A Loom can be crafted using 2 Wooden Planks and 2 ..."
    answers:
      - "Strings"
      - "String"
  - question: "A Redstone Comparator can be crafted using 3 Stone, 3 Redstone Torches, and 1 ..."
    answers:
      - "Nether Quartz"
  - question: "How many Beetroots do you need for one Beetroot Soup?"
    answers:
      - "6"
      - "six"
  - question: "3 Sticks + 2 Strings + 1 Iron Ingot + 1 Tripwire Hook = ..."
    answers:
      - "Crossbow"
  - question: "What items can be crafted into sticks, besides Wooden Planks?"
    answers:
      - "Bamboo"
  - question: "Leather can be crafted using 4 ..."
    answers:
      - "Rabbit Hide"
  - question: "How many Iron Nuggets do you need to craft one Iron Block?"
    answers:
      - "81"
      - "eighty one"
      - "eighty-one"
      - "eightyone"
  - question: "How many Gold Nuggets can you craft out of one stack of Gold Blocks?"
    answers:
      - "5184"
  - question: "What can you craft using only a Honey Bottle?"
    answers:
      - "Sugar"
  - question: "A Composter can be crafted using 7 ..."
    answers:
      - "Wooden Slabs"
      - "Wooden Slab"
      - "Wood slabs"
      - "Wood slab"
  - question: "It used to be possible to craft Chainmail Armor out of what?"
    answers:
      - "Fire"
  - question: "9 Ice Blocks = 1 ..."
    answers:
      - "Packed Ice"
  - question: "Snow Blocks can be crafted using ..."
    answers:
      - "Snowballs"
      - "Snowball"
  - question: "Mossy Stone Bricks can be crafted by combining either Stone Bricks and Moss Blocks, or Stone Bricks and ..."
    answers:
      - "Vines"
      - "Vine"
  - question: "How many Ice Blocks do you need to craft one Blue Ice Block?"
    answers:
      - "81"
      - "eighty one"
      - "eighty-one"
      - "eightyone"
  - question: "4 Packed Mud can be crafted into 4 ..."
    answers:
      - "Mud Bricks"
      - "Mud Brick"